<?xml version="1.0"?>
<content collectionGUID="63F913E4-C0D6-43F1-B375-23842844428F">
  <lastEdited clientType="local-build-20131031" date="2013-10-31 19:25:12 -0700"/>
  <textBox id="generic-header-attribute" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>No fear, do your research. Use logic WISELY.</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-title-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>The not-so Affordable Healthcare Act</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-datefield-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Thursday, October 10, 2013</richText>
  </textBox>
  <textBox id="generic-body-attributes" dynamic="no" visible="yes">
    <richText>Today is day ten of the government shutdown, with the national parks, FDA, NASA, and the CDC are all still closed.  This quest to shutdown the &#x201C;Affordable Care Act&#x201D; have been initiated by a Senator Tex Cruz (R-TX) have awakened the people do the downsides of the Affordable Care Act.  The piece of legislation that was flawed from the start and continued to spiral downward as time progressed.  In a world where people get their primary news from Facebook, and Twitter we have raised an era of difference, what we need is alliance.  We can take points from both sides to re-write a completely new set of codes to reform healthcare, not to use government provided socialized medicine.  I&#x2019;m not screaming Shutdown the government, or shutdown Social Security, In a system that thrives in balance, the left and right wings have been corrupted.  The Private sector has already proven itself, just look at SpaceX and various other private enterprises accomplishing feats from  launching private probes into earth orbit as well as manned spaceflight.  I have one question to the good people who support President Obama, Nancy Pelosi and The Affordable Care Act,  Who is going to pay for all of this medical care?  If you can sign up regardless of your condition, I could simply pay the fine until I get sick, then join as I could not be refused.  Sure it&#x2019;s easy to sign up for but, the &#x201C;care&#x201D; will not be efficient. &#xD;&#xD;A few possible solutions to this problem: More doctors.  Anyone who has taken any economics class will tell you about Supply and Demand, and the all important Market Clearing Price.  The Capitalist System has worked so far, why are you so eager to give it up.  Do you wan&#x2019;t to be a part time nation?  Do YOU want to leave an IMPACT on future generations.  You pride yourself on caring and being &#x201C;politically correct&#x201D;, that is the most BS I have ever heard.  There is no political correctness.  Yes you are entitled to your opinion however you don&#x2019;t have to force it on everyone.  However if your system is so great, it shouldn't have to be imposed by law onto everyone, they should go willingly, there is no need for&lt;a href="http://www.irs.gov/irb/2011-02_IRB/ar10.html"&gt; forcibly imposed healthcare&lt;/a&gt;.&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;&#xD;</richText>
  </textBox>
</content>
